Clarinet is a command line tool for Clarity smart contract development.

For Clarinet documentation, refer to https://docs.hiro.so/clarinet/introduction. Report any issues here https://github.com/hirosystems/clarinet/issues/new.

Usage: clarinet <COMMAND>

Commands:
  completions   Generate shell completions scripts
  new           Create and scaffold a new project
  contracts     Subcommands for working with contracts
  requirements  Interact with contracts deployed on Mainnet
  chainhooks    Subcommands for working with chainhooks (deprecated)
  deployments   Manage contracts deployments on Simnet/Devnet/Testnet/Mainnet
  console       Load contracts in a REPL for an interactive session
  check         Check contracts syntax
  integrate     Start a local Devnet network for interacting with your contracts from your browser
  devnet        Subcommands for Devnet usage
  lsp           Get Clarity autocompletion and inline errors from your code editor (VSCode, vim, emacs, etc)
  format        Format clarity code files
  dap           Step by step debugging and breakpoints from your code editor (VSCode, vim, emacs, etc)
  help          Print this message or the help of the given subcommand(s)

Options:
  -h, --help
          Print help (see a summary with '-h')

  -V, --version
          Print version
